Welcome to the demonic
realm, and my territory!
Now, let us battle at our full power!
Decisive Battle
Now go, and don't look back.
Fio...
I'm so scared that I don't know what to do.
I don't want to hurt anyone,
but I don't want to be hurt either.
I wish I could just run away.
I need to go after Fio.
Huh... Why?
Why?
I guess I really don't want to fight.
I'm such a coward!
Plant Bind!
He's wide open!
Energy Bolt!
How's that?
Not bad. That was some decent teamwork.
What? It didn't hurt him at all?
But it's not enough!
What is that?
I can transform myself at will.
My armor and my axe are
part of my body as well.
Everyone—Ow!
But my body... finally moved.
Dolan...
Please give me strength.
I don't want to hurt anybody.
But...
I want to see people getting hurt even less!
Are you done, my elven warriors?
Brother!
Rest in piece, elven warrior!
Don't!
Earth Chain Bind!
Celina? Why are you here?
I can still fight!
So you're back, lamia.
That's the spirit!
Jalaam!
Wow, Celina.
Very nice.
How about this, girlie?!
Titan Fist!
Celina...
Stand back, Fio.
My mana output is scary
even for me right now.
O-Okay, got it.
That's it, lamia. This is great.
I'll respond in kind.
I've made up my mind.
Gaia Strike!
O snake blood that flows within me.
I'll stop you!
O snake curse that binds my very soul.
How could this be?
A lamia's cursed eyes froze me?
I beseech you and your wretched nature.
Raise a cursed battle cry
and douse all life with your venom!
Eun Jalaam!
I am not going down!
And I cannot afford to lose!
What? It's almost like a dragon...
She won.
She actually beat a demon.
I did it, Dolan.
What a sad place.
You called this your territory,
but I don't even see a castle here.
I lead a mercenary's life. I am
merely a hired hand of the royals.
Please excuse the lack of pomp.
It doesn't bother me.
Here, I can swing my blade
to my heart's content.
Oh, the heart of a progenitor dragon,
one of the seven original dragons...
You are the dragon who was more feared
than the wretched gods themselves.
Now, see if you can handle me at my best!
I'll grant your desire.
But it'll cost you your entire existence.
My blades shall cut you down to size!
Cry, heavens... Heavenly Death Throes!
Roar, earth... Earthly Death Tremors!
Heaven and Earth Rending!
I'll slice it all apart.
This is the reward for all my waiting!
Chris!
Oh, it's you all.
Diadora? Weren't you part of the Gio squad?
My apologies.
I had a score to settle
with one of the demons.
Oh, for crying out loud...
Anyway, where's Dolan?
He went ahead to the portal.
We should hurry, too.
I see. So they went to the
demonic realm to battle.
What is this?
Lady Olivia.
The demon soldiers in the
area have been dealt with.
Where did that powerful demon
guarding the portal go?
It seems he and Dolan went
to the demonic realm.
What? He returned to the demonic realm?
Is this not a golden opportunity for us?
True. If we close the portal now,
the forest will be saved.
But...
Come on, now. Dolan is
still there fighting.
Yes, I'm aware that it isn't
the right thing to do.
But righteousness isn't worth risking
the lives of everyone here.
Are you serious?
I'm not done yet.
Behold the sword techniques
I spent all my years perfecting.
Huh? You're destroying the portal?
Do you realize that Dolan is
fighting on the other side?
The top priority of this operation
is to restore peace to the forest.
We won't have a better chance to do it.
I don't agree with leaving him to die.
Are you serious, Father?
We have no choice.
Powerful reinforcements may be
on their way here as we speak.
And if Dolan were to lose...
He won't!
D-Dolan would never lose!
I understand wanting to
put your faith in him,
but what guarantee do we have?
W-Well...
I agree that Dolan won't lose.
And why's that?
Just a hunch.
A hunch?
I'm sorry, but that's not very convincing.
He's putting his life on
the line to fight for you!
If he were scared for his life,
he could've waited for the
kingdom's forces to arrive.
But he's fighting to protect the
inhabitants of the Forest of Ente!
Celina's right.
If we close the portal now,
we'll disgrace ourselves for all eternity.
And that's no different to
being wiped out by the demons!
Yep, yep.
You kids...
Sigh.
What was I so afraid of?
I suppose victory is not the
be all and end all in this battle.
Very well. We'll stake our
future on Dolan's victory.
Dolan...
Can you see through the flash of my blades?
Death by Four Thousand Slashes!
Oho?
I'll have your head!
I'm not about to let you have it so easily.
I'm not done!
It's over.
My best wasn't good enough.
But your aura and fighting spirit
were as good as Ardes's.
I am... truly... honored...
Consider my blade to represent the
forest folk whose lives you took and perish.
Understood.
But I... regret... nothing...
Rest well, irredeemable fallen war god.
Found you!
There you are, at last!
I knew you weren't gone forever.
Nothing could make me happier than
getting to play with you again.
Wait for me, Dolly.
Dolan!
Celina. You're okay.
Right back at you, Dolan.
Victory is ours!
Yeah!
I didn't expect you to
throw such a big party.
We may be rebuilding, but we can't
bid our friends a quiet farewell.
It's too bad, but I suppose
there's no avoiding it.
Tada!
Don't they both look amazing?
Traditional elven dancer attire!
P-Please stop staring.
Um... Wh-What do you think?
Getting to see you two beauties in such
charming attire is a huge reward in itself.
You don't mince words, Dolan.
Huh? I only stated what I thought.
Miss Christina.
May we talk to you?
Uh, well...
Dolan, you know what to do next, right?
Celina, may I have this dance?
Of course!
How are your wounds, Celina?
All healed.
That's good to hear.
You know, I tried to run
away from the battle.
I ran my mouth, but I couldn't do anything.
But you stayed and fought, did you not?
That's what makes you strong.
Hold your head high.
It was all thanks to you.
When I thought I couldn't go on,
I held that magic crystal you gave me tight,
and it felt like you were
there and you had my back.
I'm happy I could be of help to you.
You say these things so casually.
You really don't get it.
Neither do I, honestly.
Have some more, Dolan...
That boy was kinder
And stronger than anyone
As the days passed by
He became a young man and a hero
Together with the white dragon
He defeated the dragon of evil
The world hailed the spirits of the two
It was saved by the bond
between the hero and dragon
You were listening, Dolan?
I'm guessing that was a song about the hero.
Yes, that's right. Sorry you
had to hear my awful singing.
Please, that was beautiful.
Where did you learn that song?
It's been passed down by
family for generations.
Your family?
I see...
Did you not like it?
No, I loved it, actually.
But I was wondering what happened after
they defeated the dragon of evil.
Oh, what happens next?
If there is more, I'd love to hear it.
I'm sorry. That's all there is to the song.
The hero and his party, along with the
white dragon, defeat the dragon of evil.
The end.
I see. That's too bad.
Say, Dolan.
What do you think happened to the hero
and the white dragon in the end?
Well...
No matter how it ended for them,
the white dragon must have treasured
its friendship with the hero.
For some reason, I'm sure of it.
Yeah?
First the incident in Galoa, and now here.
That's twice you've helped me out now.
Sheer happenstance.
Have you decided to join
the magic academy yet?
I'm sure it would be a very
fruitful experience for you.
Let me think about it some
more. It does intrigue me.
I hope to hear a positive response.
Dolan.
For you.
They're black rose seeds.
You can use them in magic potions.
Wow, now that's a pleasant surprise.
Thank you, Diadora.
Aside from that, I want to show my
gratitude to you in particular.
Wha?!
D-Diadora? What are you doing?!
Oh, just my way of saying thanks.
It's the least I could do
after Dolan saved my life.
E-Even I haven't gotten that far yet...
We're back!
You two did great.
And to think we only set out to
investigate the change in the forest.
Let's go report to the chief
after leaving our things.
There's so much we have to tell everyone.
Next Episode